听力材料第一节。
听下面五段对话，每段对话后有一个小题，
从题中所给的
B, 2. So, are you doing anything this evening?
三个选项中选出。
五，最佳选项。
听完每段对话后，你都有十秒钟的时间来回答有关小题和阅读下一小题。
每段对话仅读一遍。
The new James Bond film is on at the cinema.
3. our plane will arrive at 11.
11? That's two hours from now.
It's long enough to watch a movie.
4. Excuse me, I'm looking for a pair of dark blue jeans.
5. We've been waiting for for an hour.
I'm hungry. B, I'm going to the library on Saturday morning.
第二节。
听下面三段对话或独白。
每段对话或独白后有几个小题，
从题中所给的
三个选项中选出最佳选项。
听每段对话或独白前。
你将有时间阅读各小题，
每小题五秒钟。
听完后，各小题将给出五秒钟的作答时间。
每段对话或独白读两遍。
听下面一段对话，回答第六至第八三个小。
题。
现在，你有十五秒钟的时间阅读这三个小题。
Have you got any plans for the afternoon?
Yes, I have.
I'm going to finish my science project, but maybe we can meet up in the evening.
I can't, I'm afraid.
I'm having a family party.
That's a shame.
Do you want to do something on Sunday?
Sure. The afternoon is better for me.
I may go for a bike ride with my sister in the morning.
Actually, I'm going boating with some friends on Sunday afternoon, but you're
welcome to join us.
Thanks. I'd love to.
See you on Sunday.
What are you up to at the weekend?
I'm going to the library on Saturday morning.
Have you got any plans for the afternoon?
Yes, I have.
I'm going to finish my science project, but maybe we can meet up in the evening.
I can't, I'm afraid.
I'm having a family party.
That's a shame.
Do you want to do something on Sunday?
Sure. The afternoon is better for me.
I may go for a bike ride with my sister in the morning.
Actually, I'm going boating with some friends on Sunday afternoon, but you're
welcome to join us.
Thanks. I'd love to.
See you on Sunday.
听下面一段对话，回答第九至第十一三个小题。
现在你有。
十五秒钟的时间阅读这三个小题
Welcome to Live from London.
Today, I'm in King's King's Cross talking to people about food.
Do you eat healthy food, Emily?
I try to.
I like it when I do, but I try and have a healthy meal and everything.
But yeah, I think I do.
I try to.
What do you think is healthy food and what isn't?
I'd say healthy food is more natural things, not lots of oil and sugar.
And the opposite would be drinks and ice cream and things like that.
But it's fine to have it sometimes.
What do you usually have for breakfast?
I have fresh fruit and yogurt because they're really good for your health of the
mind. So that's what I do.
Welcome to Live from London.
Today, I'm in King's Cross talking to people about food.
Do you eat healthy food, Emily?
I try to.
I like it when I do, but I try and have a healthy meal and everything.
But yeah, I think I do.
I try to.
What do you think is healthy food and what isn't?
I'd say healthy food is more natural things, not lots of oil and sugar.
And the opposite would be drinks and ice cream and things like that.
But it's fine to have it sometimes.
What do you usually have for breakfast?
I have fresh fruit and yogurt because they're really good for your health of the
mind. So that's what I do.
听下面一段独白。
回答第十二至第十五四个小。
题。
现在，你有二十秒钟的时间阅读这四个小题。
Thank you. I'm sure everyone here knows all about the terrible sickness Ebola, which
makes thousands and thousands of people in Africa sick.
There have been a few cases in Europe and America, but the problem is still mainly
in African countries.
At the moment, scientists are working very hard to find new medicines because normal
medicines don't work.
People don't catch the sickness from the air, but from touching other people who
have it. This makes it hard for and nurses who are caring for the sick.
We really need to help them.
They need more money for research hospitals and more doctors.
So that's why I'm talking to you today.
The school is planning to have a walk to raise money next weekend.
The event will start at the school on Saturday morning at 1030.
It will go through the forest and across the hills to Brockfield.
The fastest walkers should take about three hours, but we hope the last people will
arrive in Brockfield before 430.
So get your walking shoes on and join us on Saturday to help fight Ebola.
I'm sure everyone here knows all about the terrible sickness Ebola, which makes
thousands and thousands of people in Africa sick.
I'm sure the terrible sickness Ebola, thousands I'm sure
I'm sure about the sickness thousands people makes sick.
I'm sure everyone here knows all about the terrible sickness Ebola, which makes
thousands and thousands of people in Africa
I'm